http://www.solutionzinc.com/privacy-policy

About
Corporate Information:
Why Solutionz?
Locations
Industries:
AV Integration
Integrated Solutions:
Network Security & Infrastructure
Physical Layer Infrastructure (PLi)
Critical Systems & Power Cooling
Commercial Security Infrastructure
Unified Communication as a Service
DAS - WLAN Enterprise Solution
A/V Partners:
Shop Headsets, Phones & Peripherals
Cloud Solutions:
Zoom Videoconferencing
Collaboration Partners:
S.C.U.D.™ Cybersecurity Services
Cybersecurity Maturity Model Certification (CMMC)
Corporate Information
Why Solutionz?
Network Security & Infrastructure
Physical Layer Infrastructure (PLi)
PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT
This is the web site of Solutionz, Inc. Our postal address is 901 Bringham Ave., Los Angeles, CA 90049. We can be reached via e-mail at info@solutionzinc.com or you can reach us by telephone at (888) 815-6128.
Personal Information
For each visitor to our web site, our server may automatically recognize the visitor's domain name, IP address or ISP. Email addresses and other direct, non-anonymous contact information is only accessible when provided voluntarily by the visitor through interaction with one of our contact forms.
The anonymous visitor information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site, to customize the content and/or layout of our site for each individual visitor, or to notify consumers about updates to our web site, and not will not be shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Contact Forms
Personal information collected through all of the voluntary data collection forms on the Solutionz, Inc. web site is used to contact the user with information they have requested. Should the user not have requested any additional information at the time of filling out the form, Solutionz uses the provided personal information to follow up with the user to ensure they have received all information, quotes, and specs they were looking for upon filling out the form. All personal information collected by Solutionz remains private property of Solutionz and is not released to any third party company.
Email
Each email sent from Solutionzinc.com contains information on unsubscribing from lists to which a user may have previously opted-in.
If you have difficulty unsubscribing via the standard channels, and do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us email at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
Postal Mail
If you supply us with your postal address you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, emailing us at the above address, or writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.
Telephone Numbers
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only be contacted for the express purpose stated at the time the phone number was requested. You will never receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events.
Advertising
At this time, Solutionz does not partner with or purchase services from ad serving companies
Changes to this Policy
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to their own unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) and contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain for them.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
